# SINDHU PURNOMO AJI

sindhupurnomoaji@gmail.com | +6285726611097 Sragen, January 01, 2002 Karangtengah RT.41, RW.16 Masaran, Masaran, Sragen, Central Java



## **SUMMARY**

A fresh graduate in Computer Science with in-depth knowledge in web development and IoT technology. Possesses strong analytical skills in designing solutions and implementing changes. Experienced in working in teams, collaborating effectively to achieve project goals and enhance user interaction. Interested in graphic design, which supports the ability to create attractive and functional interfaces. Committed to continuous learning and growth in the information technology industry.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Member of KPPS for the Regional Election

NOV 2024 - DEC 2024

- Served as Sirekap to collect and recap the voting results.
- suring the accuracy and consistency of the entered data.
- Completed administrative tasks and reported the recapitulation results.
- Collaborated with other team members to ensure the data collection and recapitulation process ran smoothly and effectively.

#### Member of KPPS for the Presidential and Vice Presidential Election

**JAN 2024 - FEB 2024** 

- Served as Sirekap to collect and recap the voting results.
- suring the accuracy and consistency of the entered data.
- Completed administrative tasks and reported the recapitulation results.
- Collaborated with other team members to ensure the data collection and recapitulation process ran smoothly and effectively.

# PT Sapta Cakra Manunggal Yogyakarta (Internship)

AUG 2023 - JAN 2024

- Developed a website integrated with Internet of Things (IoT) technology.
- Designed a mobile application to enhance user interaction and accessibility.
- Collaborated with the team to ensure effective project execution and integration of features.

### **Anugerah Jaya Printing (Internship)**

**JUL 2018 - NOV 2018** 

- Edited graphic designs using CorelDRAW for various printing projects.
- Executed finishing processes on MMT products, including cutting and final touches.
- Collaborated with the team to ensure quality and timely completion of projects.

## **EDUCATION**

#### **Bachelor of Computer Scince with Honours**

**SEP 2020 - SEP 2024** 

Duta Bangsa University of Surakarta

- · Major in Informatics Engineering
- Thesis on "Development of Charity Box Security System in Mosque Raya Assalam Masaran Based on IoT (Internet of Things)"

# **Vocational High School in Software Development**

**SEP 2017 - SEP 2020** 

State Vocational High School 1 Plupuh

• Relevant coursework in Software Development

# **SCIENTIFIC PUBLICATION**

 Development of Charity Box Security System in Mosque Raya Assalam Masaran Based on IoT (Internet of Things) 2024

Infotech: Journal of Technology Information, 10(1), 113-120

• Perancangan Aplikasi E-Commerce Grocery Berbasis Mobile 2022

Proceedings of the National Seminar on Information Technology and Business, 452-454

### **CERTIFICATION & ADDITIONAL SKILLS**

Certificate of Competence in Junior Web Programming 2024
National Professional Certification Board (BNSP)

• Certificate of Competence in English Proficiency Test 2024 (TOEIC Score : 510)

Language Training Center Duta Bangsa University

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- Web Technologies : HTML, CSS, Laravel, Bootstrap.
- Database : MySQL.
- Tools: Visual Studio Code, Microsoft Office, Canva, Coreldraw.
- Languages: English and Bahasa Indonesia.

### **SOFT SKILLS**

- Dicipline
- Teamwork
- Time Management
- Problem Solving
- Creativity
- Adaptability